randomwalktab.com 2019-03-14

# Privacy Policy | RandomWalk Tab

Aztec Media Inc ("Aztec Media") owns and operates the RandomWalk Tab extension ("RandomWalk Tab"). Aztec Media is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its user community. The intent of this privacy policy is to detail the information Aztec Media may gather about individuals who uses RandomWalk Tab, how that information is used, and Aztec Media's disclosure practices. Please note that this policy applies only to the RandomWalk Tab, and not to the Web sites of other companies or organizations to which we provide links or to any software that may be downloaded from the RandomWalk Tab.

### Anonymous User Information

Aztec Media collects some anonymous information each time you use a RandomWalk Tab so we can improve the overall quality of your online experience. We collect your IP address, referral data, and browser and platform type. You do not have to register with Aztec Media before we can collect this anonymous information.

The RandomWalk Tab do not require you to share information that identifies you personally, such as your name or e-mail address, in order for you to use the RandomWalk Tab. The RandomWalk Tab assign an anonymous ID number to your requests and links the following additional data to that number: the date and time you visited the RandomWalk Tab, your search terms, and the links upon which you choose to click. Like most standard Web site servers, we use log files to collect and store this anonymous user information. Aztec Media analyzes the information to examine trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

### Individual User Information

From time-to-time the RandomWalk Tab request information from you that may identify you personally in addition to the anonymous information described above. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name, e-mail address, shipping address, and zip code), and demographic information (such as age, gender, occupation, and household income). Aztec Media will not use or disclose your individual user information except as described in this privacy policy. Aztec Media collects individual user information in the following ways from different RandomWalk Tab: 

### Surveys or Contests

From time to time, Aztec Media may conduct surveys or contests on a RandomWalk Tab. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose individual user information to the RandomWalk Tab. Contest information will be shared with the contest or survey sponsors to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of the RandomWalk Tab. We may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests. These companies may use your personal information to help the RandomWalk Tab communicate with you about offers from the RandomWalk Tab and our marketing partners. Such third parties do not have Aztec Media's permission to use your personally identifiable information for any secondary purpose.

### Tell-A-Friend

If you elect to use our referral service for informing a friend about any of our sites, we ask you for your friend's name and e-mail address. Aztec Media will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit the RandomWalk Tab. Aztec Media does not store the information related to your friends and the one-time e-mail sent pursuant to your input will be our only contact with that person for such input.

### Correspondence

If you contact Aztec Media, we may keep a record of that correspondence and we may collect your e-mail address.

### Third Party Information Gathering

The RandomWalk Tab include content and ads from third parties that may perform user activity tracking other than that described herein. For more information about each third party content provider, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please refer to such third party advertiser's privacy policy.

The RandomWalk Tab contain links to other sites on the Web. Please be aware that Aztec Media is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

### Sharing

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a criminal investigation, a court order, or legal process served on our Web site. We may also share your personal information if we believe it is necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Aztec Media's or such RandomWalk Tab's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

RandomWalk Tab may use third party service providers to serve ads and e-mails on our behalf. These companies may use technologies to measure the effectiveness of ads and e-mails and use information about your visits to the RandomWalk Tab so that we can provide a better search experience to you. For this purpose, we may also provide these third party service providers anonymous information about your site navigation.

### Mergers; Business Transitions

In the event Aztec Media goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

### Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement in places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

If, however, we are going to use Individually Identifiable Information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

Aztec Media Inc  
Post Office Box 51968, Limassol, Cyprus.
